Are you nervous?
緊張してるかな?
Hey, you're doing it.
ね、してるよね
After all, it's because I'm around cool people.
や っぱりね、かっこいい人近くにいるからだよね
yes.
はい
Do you really think so?
本当に思ってる?
You don't think so.
思ってないでしょ
Hey, I'm a little nervous right now.
ちょっとさ、今緊張してるじゃん
Me too, I'd like to relieve your tension.
ちょっと俺もね、緊張解いてあげたいのよ
Can I do a little interview?
ちょっとインタビューしてもいいかな?
yes.
はい
Is it okay for about 30 hours?
30時間くらい平気?
Just a little more.
もうちょっと
It's a little shorter.
もうちょっと短い
Is 20 hours enough?
20時間でいいの?
Just to be quick, let me tell you a little bit.
ちょっと手短にね、ちょっと話すんだけど
yes.
はい
What type of work do you do?
どういう系のさ、お仕事されてるんですか?
Part-time job, etc.
バイトとかで
Yes, I have a part-time job.
うん、あ、バイトなんだ
What do you do part-time?
何のバイトしてるの?
I have a part-time job at a call center.
コールセンターのバイトしてる
That's right.
そうなんだ
Oh, so you're dealing with it?
え、じゃあ対応してるの?
now.
今
yes.
はい
Oh, I can't see anything.
え、なんか見えないね
What, can you speak properly?
え、ちゃんと話せるの?
No, I'll talk.
いや、話しますよ
Try it.
やってみてよ
Oh, no.
え、いやだ
Brrrrrrrr, brurrrrrr, something like that.
ブルルルル、ブルルルル、みたいな
Brrrrrrrrr, something like that.
ブルルルル、みたいな
It's getting better.
なってるなってる
Unless it's 3 calls, it's basically right?
3コールでないと基本でしょ?
perhaps.
多分
Brrrrrr.
ブルルル
hello.
もしもし
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It must be really embarrassing.
めっちゃ恥ずかしかってんじゃん
It's cute.
可愛いね
Well, what's the ratio of men and women like?
え、それさ、男女の比率どんな感じなの?
It seems like there are a lot of women there.
めっちゃ女の人が多い感じですね
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
About 80% women?
女性8割くらい?
Are there not many men?
男性あんまりいないの?
There are some, but they are really few.
いれはいるけど、本当に少ないです
That's right.
そうなんですね
Isn't it tough in a vertical society when there are so many women?
女性多いとさ、縦社会厳しいんじゃないの?
No, but I don't think I'll have much of a chance to get involved.
いや、でもそんなにあんまり関わる機会がないかも
I see.
なるほどね
So, you don't go out to eat with your colleagues?
で、一緒に同僚とご飯とか行ったりしないんだ?
I won't go there.
行ったりしないですね
So, I guess I'll go home as soon as I'm done?
じゃ、終わったらすぐ帰っちゃうみたいな感じ?
It's a little lonely, you know.
ちょっと寂しいね、それね
Maybe so.
そうかもしれない
Well, then after that, we won't go out together or anything.
じゃあ、そしたらその後さ、一緒に遊び行ったりとかもしないんだ
hey?
ね?
I don't think so.
し ないですね
That's right.
そうなんだね
Well, no, it might be a demon wind.
まあ、違う、魔風かもしれないね
It's like that right now, you might be busy.
今そういうね、サバサバしてるかもしれないですよね
I see.
なるほどね
Do you enjoy your work?
仕事楽しいですか?
Yes, is it fun?
はい、楽しいですか?
Well, it's fun.
まあ、楽しいです
I see.
なるほどね
Well then, will there be any encounters?
じゃあさ、出会いとかあったりする?
There are no encounters at all.
出会いとかは全然ないですね
Is that so?
そうなんですか?
What kind of man is your type?
どういった男の人がタイプなんですか?
Someone other than me please.
僕以外でお願いします
A kind and clean person.
やさしくて、清潔感ある人
Who is your favorite celebrity?
芸能人って誰が好きなの?
If you're a celebrity...
芸能人だと...
Seriously, celebrities like Ryo Yoshizawa.
芸能人はまじで、吉沢亮とか
Isn't it really cool?
めちゃくちゃかっこいいじゃないかい?
Not much at all.
もう、全然ちょっとね
Celebrities are different.
芸能人は別だから
I see.
なるほどね
Do you have a boyfriend now?
今、彼氏いるのか?
I'm not there.
いないです
Oh, he's not there.
あ、いないんだ
How long have you been gone?
どれぐらいいないの?
It's been about a year now.
もう1年ぐらいです
Ah, that's right.
あー、そうなんだ
It seems like you're not good at it.
お手そうなのにね
so.
そんなに
I see.
なるほどね
But haven't you heard anything from them?
でも、あっちから言われたりしてこないの?
I don't really meet anyone, so it doesn't happen very often.
本当に出会いがないから、あんまりないですね
You're asleep, aren't you?
眠ってるんですね
There's this cute girl at the call center.
コールセンターにこういう可愛い子が
Will you come if I call?
コールしたら来てくれる?
What do you think?
どうかな?
Ah, maybe that's a little harsh?
あー、ちょっと厳しいのかな?
I see.
なるほど
Well then, well then.
じゃあ、まあね
What kind of date would you like to go on?
どういうデートで行きたいとかあったりするかな?
On a date.
デートで
It's okay to go on a date that you've had fun with before.
今まで楽しかったデートでもいいよ
Something classic, like Disney.
なんか、定番だけどディズニーとか
Hoi hoi hoi.
ほいほいほい
theme park.
テーマパーク
Theme park?
テーマパーク?
It's a theme park.
テーマパークね
What time will you start if we go together?
一緒に行くと、何時から?
From the morning.
朝から
5am?
朝5時?
Even before becoming a member.
会員前から
Oh, that's pretty serious.
あ、結構ガチだね
Yes, yes, yes.
はいはいはい
Isn't it going to change a lot?
結構変わるんじゃないの?
That, and personality too.
それ、性格も
Will it become like a wai-wai?
ワイワイみたいになるの?
Yes, that's right.
そう、そうですね
I might have a lot of fun.
結構はしゃぐかも
Hey, I can't see that atmosphere.
ね え、その雰囲気見えないっすね
I like the gap a bit.
ちょっとギャップいいね
I see.
なるほど
Well then, I guess I'll go with you.
そしたらね、一緒に行くとするとするじゃないですか
Where do you want to ride?
どこ乗りたいの?
Yeah, I don't know, but I can't really ride the screaming type.
えー、なんか、でもあんま絶叫系乗れないから
So, is 50 episodes of Pooh's Honey Hunt okay?
じゃあ、プーさんのハニーハント50回でいいの?
Pooh's Honey Hunt and It's a small
プーさんのハニーハントと、It's a small
world
Repeat?
繰 り返し?
repetition.
繰り返し
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Can you go there?
そこ行ける?
That's it.
そこまで
Is it dangerous?
やばいかな
I see.
なるほどね
I wouldn't be like that.
私、あんまならばないもんね
I see.
なるほど
Well, that's good.
まあね、いいよね
Well, then I'll go there with you.
じゃあ、そしたらそこ一緒に行くじゃん
Hey, what about food?
ね え、ご飯とかどうするの?
As for the rice, well, that's about it.
ご飯とかはまあ、その辺の
Kiros, through the nose?
キロス、鼻から?
Do you eat Kiros through your nose?
鼻からキロス食べるの?
Can you go?
行ける?
Can you really go to a theme park like that?
本当に、そういうテーマパークも行けるの?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
I see.
なるほど
Yes, yes.
はいはい
Well then, let's come together.
じゃあ、一緒にね
Eat some food.
ご飯食べて
Well then, it's spinning, right?
じゃあ、回るじゃないですか
Will it last until the end?
終焉までいるのかな?
Until the end.
終焉まで
Look at the parade.
パレード見て
So what do you do after that?
じゃあ、その後どうするの?
After that, I went home or stayed at a nearby hotel.
その後は、家帰ったり、近くのホテル泊まったり
Is it okay if I stay at a hotel?
ホテル泊まっちゃっていいの?
Yeah.
うん
Well, you should tell me you're already staying at a hotel.
それでさ、もうホテル泊ってあるんだけどって言われた方がいいの
Well, naturally, there's still a sequel theme park.
か、 自然に、ちょっとまださ、 続きのテーマパークあるんだ
I think it would be better if it was a bit like a gag.
よね、 みたいな感じで、ちょっとギャグ的な感じで行った方が嬉
Is it true?
しい のか
No, it's standing up, but it might be more exciting.
いや、立ってあるんだけど、の方がドキドキするかも
That makes sense.
それちょっと、なるほどね
Ryo-kun, I was imagining that.
それちょっと、りょうくん想像したっしょ、
perhaps.
たぶん
Well, the person behind me said,
それ、ねえ、ちょっと後ろの人が言ったら、
Isn't it a bit necessary?
ちょっと逆必要じゃないの?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
You look so serious, I've already booked a hotel.
すごいマジ顔でさ、ホテル予約してるからさ、
I think it was at 11:30.
11時半にしたみたいな
Rather than sounding like it's not going to happen very often,
ちょっとそうそう行かないみたいな感じで言われるよりさ、
The one who said it as a bit of a joke is still
ちょっとギャグで言われた方がまだ、
Terika, on the other hand, feels like she wants to be taken seriously.
テリカは、あれなんだ、逆に真剣に言われたい感じなんだ
I see.
なるほどね
So, we're going to the same hotel together.
で、一緒ホテル行くじゃないですか
When I went to the hotel, I said, ``Hey, what should I do?''
ホテル行ったらさ、ねえ、やることって言ったらさ、
It's going to be limited.
限られてくるよね
What are you doing?
何するの?
Hey, that's not what I meant.
ねえ、そういうことじゃないんです
Oh, don't watch TV.
あ、テレビ見るんじゃないってね
I see.
なるほどね
It's quite naughty.
結構エッチですね
I see.
なるほど
Today, Gochinchin Land opens its doors.
今日ね、ごちんちんランドね、開幕するわけですね
I might get angry a little more, though.
もうちょっとね、怒られるかもしれないけどね
So, if that happens, yes.
じゃあ、そうなったとして、 はい
Well then, I'll go with you.
じゃあ、一緒に行きますと
Well, that's the kind of atmosphere it was.
まあ、そういう雰囲気になりましたと
What do you think? Do you like sex?
どうですか、エッチは好きですか?
I like it already.
もう、好きです
Ah, I like it.
あ、好きなんだ
yes.
はい
Which one would you choose between S and M?
SとMで言ったらどっち?
If anything, it might be M.
どっちかと言えば、Mかも
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
Until now, tell me about the exciting sex you've had.
今までさ、興奮したエッチ教えてよ
Well, it's kind of like hiding in bed or something.
えーっと、なんか、寝隠しとか、結構
I like it.
好きなんだ
Yeah, that's right.
えー、そうなんだ
Why are you excited?
なんで興奮するの?
I don't know what's going on, I don't know what's going to happen to me,
なんか、なんだろう、何されるかわかんなくて、
It's like my heart is pounding.
ドキドキするみたいな
I see.
なるほどね
It's okay to feel a little strange.
ちょっと不思議な感じがしていいんだ
Do you do pebonany or something?
ペボナニーとかしたりするの?
Sometimes, right?
たまに、ですね
Oh, I'll do it.
あ、するんだ
yes.
はい
Is that your hand?
それを手ですか?
Is it up to your hands?
手まですか?
It's a hand.
手です
Ah, do it with your hands.
あ、手でするんだ
Eh, where should I touch it?
えー、どこ触るの?
where?
どこ?
Here it is.
ここです
Where is this place?
ここってどの辺ですか?
this?
これ?
Hey, clothes?
ねえ、服?
no.
いや
Where is it?
どこですか?
Where are you?
ど こですか?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいです
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしいですか?
Is it clothes?
服ですか?
Where does it start with clothes?
服から始まるとこですか?
yes.
はい
So, will the leader end?
で、リーダー終わるの?
Well then, just go and have a look.
じゃあ、ちょっと行ってみて
leader.
リーダー
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
You touch it.
触るんだね
If you can't hear me, say it again,
聞こえなかったらもう一回言うか、
a little bit.
ちょっと
What?
なんだ?
I'm a little hard of hearing, sorry.
ちょっと耳が悪くて、すいませんね、
I.
僕
Hey.
ねえ
I'll touch your neck.
首触ります
Oh, what are you imagining?
あ、何想像してするの?
What do you imagine?
何想像?
Eh, but.
えー、でも
I guess I don't have to think about it too much.
あ んまり何か考えてするとかないかな
I'm going to die.
死んでいくんだ
This is it.
こっちですね
But when I'm lonely and horny, I do it myself.
でも、寂しくなっててムラムラした時は自分でしちゃうの
Please call me for a moment.
ちょっと呼んでくださいよ
Me.
僕は
Hey.
ね え
It's already empty.
もう空いてるんでね
24時間
How about it?
ちょっとどう?
Did you feel a little less nervous?
緊張ちょっと解けましたか?
Wait a minute, yes.
ちょっと、はい
And then, a little more today too.
そしたらね、もうちょっと今日もね、
It's already here.
もう来てます
To Ten Park.
テンパークに
Then, a little while later, they called the cast.
そしたらちょっとね、キャスト呼んでくるんで、
This wasn't possible due to schedule constraints.
ちょっとスケジュールの都合じゃこれなかったです
Ah, that's it.
あ、そんな
sorry.
すみません
yes.
はい
I'm feeling a little like I've given birth.
ちょっと気持ち風産みたいに来ちゃってる
Yeah.
うん
I guess that's okay for a little while.
もうちょっとそれで大丈夫かな
Can I hunt for a while?
ちょっと ハントしていいですか?
Yeah.
うん
Can I pat you on the head a little?
ちょっと頭撫でてもいい?
How about a pat on the head?
頭撫でるのはどうかな?
I quite like it.
結構好きです
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
Why do you like it?
なんで好きなの?
Eh, why do you feel calm?
え、なんでなんか落ち着く?
Oh, are you calm down?
あ、落ち着いてくれてるの?
now.
今
A little Tenten.
ちょっとテンテンで
Something is telegraphing.
なんかテレる
It's cute.
可愛いね
Can I take it home?
持って帰っていい?
Did you eat it?
食べた?
And what about the ears?
そしたら耳とかどう?
It might tickle your ears.
耳結構くすぐったいかも
Does this tickle and feel good?
これはさ、くすぐった気持ちいいのか、
Is it just ticklish?
くすぐったいだけなの?
Yeah.
うん
It might feel a little better.
もうちょっと気持ちいいかも
This is a loose-eared head.
このさ、耳たぶらヘッド
Main body?
本体?
A new genre has arrived.
新しいジャンル来たね
Can I touch everything?
全部触っていい?
Yeah.
うん
It's playing, now.
奏でてるね、これで
Looks like it's more naughty than I thought.
なんか思ったよりエッチそうですね
That's right.
そうなの
How do you touch your neck?
首とかどう触る?
The neck is fine.
首は結構
Ah, I like it.
あ、好きなんだ
I wonder if it's a bit of a wait-and-see body?
結 構全身静観体だったりするのかな?
What do you think?
どうだろう?
That's naughty.
エッチだね
Hey, can I get used to it?
ちょっとさ、馴染んでいいかな?
Is this so?
こうですか?
It feels kind of weird.
なんか、変な感じ
Is there a lot of one-piece fashion like this?
こういうさ、ワンピース系のファッションが多いのかな?
Well, I guess there are quite a lot of things like this.
そうですね、こういうの結構多いかも
Are there many colors like this?
こういう色味が多いの?
White?
白とか?
What a terrible feeling?
ものとんな感じ?
There are many.
多いです
Well then, I want to check out the fashion.
じゃあちょっとね、ファッションチェックしたいんで
Can you stand for a moment?
ちょっと一瞬立てますか?
Ah, it suits you.
あ、似合ってるね
It's cute.
かわいいですね
I'll just check the time.
きっき時間ちょっとチェックするんで
is that so?
そうですか?
Sonpai, don't you hate it when I don't touch you?
ソンパイさ、触らないの嫌いじゃない?
It's better to be mixed.
混ざってる方が
It feels like you've pioneered a new genre.
また新しいジャンルをね、開拓してきた感じですね
Sorry, it's time.
すみません、きっき時間ね
Your skin is pale, really.
肌白いね、本当に
is that so?
そうですか?
Are you being very careful?
結構気をつけてるの?
I agree.
そうですね
It's such beautiful skin.
すごい綺麗な肌質だよね
Tickling feels good, doesn't it just tickle?
くすぐった気持ちいいじゃん、普通にくすぐったい?
this is?
これは?
I think this tickles.
これはくすぐったいと思う
There may be many types like this.
こういう系多いかも
That's right.
そうなんだ
I don't know much about medicine, and I don't know where to go.
ちょっと薬が分かんなくて、場所が
hey.
ね
This is what it looks like from above your pants.
パ ンツの上からこんな感じちゃうんだよね
Black, black.
黒い、黒い
The style is really nice.
スタイルめちゃくちゃいいね
It feels like a white knitwear is coming to your house.
白ニットがお家に遊びに来てるみたいな感じですよね
Ah, it's probably this short.
あ、これこんな短いんだ、多分